There is no VTB in Crimea, well, no pom yet, so this is a
ВТБ в Крыму нет ну пока нет пом так это
state
государственный
bank Hello, Popik Great, I
банк Здравствуйте о Попик Здорово Я из
'm from the city of Khmelnitsky Where do I know you,
города Хмельницкий Вы откуда я знаю тебя
well, you are my standard
что ж ты у меня стандартное
greeting script like this, I know I
приветствие скрипт такой я знаю скрипт у
have a script I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky
меня стоит Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
Where are you from? I'm from the city of Moscow  The script is like this
откуда Я из города Москвы скрипт такой
I understand if you have come in large numbers or if you are a local local
Понял понаехавший или местный местный
how local How many three
насколько местный На сколько на три
generations of places is this very important to you? This is
поколения мест вам это очень важно Это
three generations yes very important and you are a traveler
три поколе да очень важно а вы поехавший
or have come in large numbers no local local In which
или понаехал нет местный местный В каком
generation in four generations four
поколении в четыре поколения четыре
generations, that is, you before this generation
поколения то есть вас до этого поколения
lived in Sovetsky  Union is correct No, they
жили в Советском Союзе правильно Нет ещё
even lived in the Russian Empire, they
в Российской империи даже жили в
lived Yeah, how did it
Российской империи жили Ага как так
happen that they lived there in the
получилось что вот они жили там в
Russian Empire in the Soviet Union And
Российской империи в Советском Союзе А
you ended up in Ukraine Yes, it
вы на Украине оказались Да так
turns out that empires sometimes fall
получается знаете что империи бывают
apart, so the Russian
распадаются вот на распалась Российская
Empire fell apart, the Soviet Union fell apart and  now the
империя распался Советский Союз и теперь
Russian Federation is disintegrating. Yes,
распадается Российская Федерация Да
for example, Ramzan Kadyrov was born
будет например Рамзан Кадыров родился
there in the Soviet Union. He lived there. The Russian
там в Советском Союзе жил Российская
Federation will live in independent Ichkeria.
Федерация будет жить независимой Ичкерии
that is, in Crimea, that is,
например Херсон то есть в Крыму то есть
Crimea It’s on paper Kherson Well, Crimea is
Крым Это на бумаге Херсон Ну Крым
temporarily occupied there is, let’s say it Name it Name the
временно оккупирован есть давай так
Russian banks
Назови Назови Назови российские банки
that entered Crimea Sberbank the rest of the
которые зашли в Крым Сбербанк остальные
RNKB when they entered the RNKB came in Now I’ll
рнкб когда они зашли рнкб зашёл Сейчас
tell you In what year in the seventeenth year the
скажу В каком году в в семнадцатом году
Russian National
рнкб зашёл российский национальный
Commercial Bank entered the RNKB  Wait a second,
коммерческий банк Секундочку секундочку
who united many banks, they got out
который объединил многие банки они вышли
of this situation and united
из этого положения и объединили сейчас
now now What banks there are all
сейчас Какие банки там все у вас
Russian, only Sberbank Tinkov is there, I do
российские только Сбербанк Тиньков есть
n’t know for a long time Tinkova No,
не знаю давно не был Тинькова Нет
probably Why a private company And this is
наверное А почему частная компания А это
not Russia Well, just yes, why is
что не Россия Ну вот просто да почему
it private  the company can be used Here, look
она частной компании можно по Вот смотри
Why is there a private company
Почему частная компания она есть на всей
throughout Russia but it is not in Crimea
территории России но нет её в Крыму
PrivatBank Why is it not in Crimea because
ПриватБанка Почему нет в Крыму м потому
it is occupied by the Russian Federation
что он оккупирован Российской Федерации
a second you are shouting this is Crimea, it is
секундочку вы кричите это Крым с он
not under the control of Ukraine now, it is not there
сейчас не под контролем Украины там нет
so look Wait, you ran away  because
так смотри Подожди ты убежал потому что
I caught you I caught you So if
я тебя поймал я тебя поймал Вот если
Tennikov Why doesn’t Tinkov come and
теньков Почему Тиньков не заходит а
why doesn’t she come to Crimea why
почему она не заходит в Крым ча компа
private companies can afford not to
частные компании могут себе позволить не
come no there’s something else the
заходить нет там там в чём-то другом
question is true sanctions are afraid of sanctions
вопрос правда санкции боятся санкций
sanctions and that is, you see everything  Yes That is,
санкции а то есть всё видите Да То есть
you temporarily occupied this territory of
вы временно оккупировали эту территорию
sanctions, yes, that is, it turns out that your
санкций да то есть получается ваше
society Yes, did not recognize it as its
общество Да не признала её своей
territory as What does the shadow and
территорией как Причём тут тень и
society have to do with the shadows again, yes this is part of
общество ещё раз теньков да это часть
yours about tourists, wait a second, Russian
вашего об туристы секундочку российские
tourists society go to Crimea on vacation,
туристы общество в Крым отдыхать ездят
look, they also go to Turkey  they go ANO don’t
смотри они ездят и в Турцию ездят АНО не
consider Turkey really you see 2 2:0 2:0
считают Турцию правда видишь 2 2:0 2:0
yes so look Wait Once Tenkova
да так смотри Подожди Один раз тенькове
second time on trips like private
второй раз в поездках типа частны
companies can afford Listen
компании могут себе позволить Слушай
private not private Why look at
частный не частный Да почему смотри
society Yes it’s all public wait
общество Да это ж всё всё обще подожди
wait
подожди
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
wait for Wait when you blocked
подожди за Подожди когда ты заблокировал
Trump they asked Trump's Twitter before the ass
трампа спросили Твитер трампа до сраки
Why are you running away on Twitter
Зачем те что ты убегаешь на twiter
look Why don't your private companies
смотри Почему ваши частные компании не
go to Crimea because it's a private
заходят в Крым потому что это частная
company it's their personal decision Why
компания это их личное решение Почему ты
aren't you going to Crimea Please tell me
не едешь в Крым Скажи пожалуйста по
Russian Post works in  Crimea Why
Почта России работает в Крыму Почему ты
don't you go to Crimea Russian Post works in
не едешь в Крым Почта России работает в
Crimea Why don't you go to Crimea I
Крыму Почему ты не едешь в Крым Я
ask Russian Post works in Crimea
спрашиваю Почта России работает в Крыму
asked This is because it is occupied by
задавал Это потому что он оккупирован
Dolmi everything is simple, that is, Ukrainian
долми всё просто то есть украинские
citizens who are former who took ki
граждане которые бывшие которые взяли ки
paci They are idiots No they are those who
паци Они [__] Нет они те которые
are now under occupation you're
находятся сейчас под оккупации ты сейчас
living now you're running away you're running away from in I'm
живёшь ты убегаешь ты убегаешь от во
running away I'm asking questions no look I'll tell
убегаю я те задаю вопросы нет смотри я
you the scau Name the
тебе скау назови Назови структуры
large Russian structures Yes, which entered
российские крупные Да которые зашли в
Crimea I don't know for a long time You see
Крым Я не знаю давно не был Вот видишь
you don't know Let's score let's zag
ты не знаешь Давай забьём давай загу
Wait let's  Go ahead, let’s google it,
Подожди давай загу давай загугли тем
especially since you’re asking me as if I’m
более ты спрашиваешь у меня как будто я
the owner of these companies No, well, you
владелец этих компаний Не ну ты же
’re saying that it’s like Russia And here
говоришь что это типа Россия А тут
for some reason they’re not Russia Russia, they are there,
почему-то они не Росси Росси так и есть
Russian laws are in effect there,
там там российские законы действуют там
Russian money is Russia and VTB bank is
российские деньги Росси ба ВТБ банк
state-owned I  I don’t know Listen tell
государственный Я не знаю Слушай скажи
me now Let’s see let’s VTB
мне сейчас Давай посмотрим давай ВТБ
bank
банк
state bank VTB bank sri VTB
государственный банк ВТБ банк сри ВТБ
state bank is it in Crimea or
государственный банк есть он в Крыму или
not come on and google it You have
нет давай да загугли У тебя же есть
Google let’s be so interested You
Google давай тако интерес так Ты сам
look for yourself there maybe the laws don’t
посмотри там может быть законы не
apply Russian maybe maybe  the
действуют российские может быть может
Ukrainian one is still working there, I
там украинский до сих пор работае я же
don’t
не
know the documents there, they probably write
знаю документы там наверное пишут
documents
документы
when VTB writes something like this until the end of
когда вот такое пишет ВТБ до конца
2023, it will be part of it in short and
2023 года там войдёт в состав короче и
will begin to provide its own in Crimea,
начнёт оказывать свои эти в Крыму свои
that is, there is no VTB in Crimea, well, not
то есть ВТБ в Крыму нет ну пока нет
yet, then it’s state-owned  bank and that
потом так это государственный банк и то
is, you have Crimea wait stop stop you
есть у вас Крым подожди стоп стоп ты
read this they decla they
прочитал это они декла они предыдущие
declared previous years so look Why are there
года декларировать так смотри Почему
two state banks on Tenkovo
государственного банка два на тенькове
you cut something like that VTB state
ты срезал что-то так ВТБ государственный
Basya is a private company
Бася это частная компания
listen to
слушай
everything I just checked Wiki W
всё вот я проверил только что Вики Вт
state why  there is no one in Crimea, they are
государствен почему нету его в Крыму
afraid of sanctions, so this is a state
боятся санкций так это государственный
bank Well, the state bank is afraid of sanctions
банк Ну боится санкций ещё
again, you are afraid of
раз государственный банк у вас боится
sanctions, Putin’s order cannot
санкций распоряжение Путина не может
be like entering into this in Crimea Listen, it will
быть типа войти в в это в Крым Слушай
enter now I don’t know Come on in Crimea
сейчас войдёт не знаю Давай в Крыму
Come on Russian Railways Why are there no offices in Crimea And
Давай РЖД Почему нет офисов в Крыму А
there  trains run trains to other countries
туда поезда ходят поезда в другие страны
run again to China to China Russian Railways trains
ходят ещё раз в Китай в Китай РЖД поезда
run similar to Crimea run to and to
ходят схо в Крым ходят и в ж и в
Belarus run Belarus run to Crimea
Беларусь ходят Беларусь ходят в Крым
trains run to Crimea run but this is not
поезда ходят в Крым ходят но это не
the territory of Russia Russian Railways has offices there No
территория России РЖД там офисов Нет ещё
look again at Russian Railways trains  they go to Belarus in the
раз смотри РЖД поезда в Беларусь ходят в
Crimea to Belarus they go and in the Crimea they
Крыме в Беларусь ходят и в Крыме в
go to Belarus you you've crap for
Беларусь ходят ты ты обосрался уже
the third time Look you've crap for the third time
третий раз Смотри ты третий раз
your trains go to Crimea they go
обосрался ваши поезда ездят в Крым ездят
to China all this doesn't stop this is your
в Китай идт всь этого не стаёт это вашей
territory you've crap you'll now
территории ты обосрался ты сейчас будешь
say the word Popik 20  once yes VTB Google Let's Google
говорить слово Попик 20 раз да ВТБ Гугли
VTB don't jump off Come on Google
Давай Гугли ВТБ не спрыгивать Давай
VTB look there are no railway offices but
Гугли ВТБ смотри ЖД офисов нету но
trains go to Germany your trains go
поезда ездят в Германию ездят ваши
don't jump off the topic to Germany
поезда не прыгай с темы в Германию ездят
your trains go Finland trains go China
ваши поезда Финляндию ездят поезда Китай
trains go to Mongolia trains go everything come on
ездят поезда в Монголию ездят поезда всё
Loch Come on I'm waiting for VSU  Why are you zgu come on Tue
давай [__] Давай я жду ВГУ Зачем ты згу
Why are you tynu
давай Вт Зачем тыну
Tell me please why I know Come on
Скажи пожалуйста зачем зну Давай так
if you don’t give it now The answer will be
если ты сейчас не даёшь Ответ будет
considered that you slipped and went to Come on
считаться что ты слид и пошл на Давай
VTB why can’t VTB in Crimea can
ВТБ почему нету ВТБ в Крыму могут себе
afford why not VTB in Crimea
позволить почему нету ВТБ Крыму
the state said that Tinkova is a
государстве сказал что Тинькова - это
private bank  not obligated Yes, but a
частный банк частный не обязанный Да а
state bank Why in 9 years Yes in 9
государственный Почему за 9 лет Да за 9
years a private bank is already almost 10 soon yes a
лет частный банк уже почти 10 скоро
private bank is not
будет да частный банк не
there so now let’s see Why a private
зал так сейчас посмотрим Почему частный
bank oh state bank VTB did not
банк ой государственный банк ВТБ не
come It’s
зашёл
written look VTB under its own
Вот написано смотри ВТБ под своим
brand Sevastopol Crimea will not appear
брендом Севастополе Крыму не появится
instead  the credit institution
вместо этого кредитная организация
will continue to
продолжит
conduct those bank rnkb NB that is, look at the
вестию те банка рнкб НБ то есть смотри
bank again VTB bank you confirmed you
банка ещё раз банка ВТБ ты подтвердил ты
confirmed that VTB bank in Crimea
подтвердил что банка ВТБ в Крыму не
will not be accepted ban
будет годан бан
in Crimea is not and will not be Sberbank there is
в Крыму нет и не будет Сбербанк там есть
VTB I’m talking about the state bank
ВТБ я говорю про государственный банк
VTB there Sberbank again I  about VTB, you
ВТБ там сбербан ещё раз я про ВТБ ты
are running away from the state bank VTB
убегаешь государственного банка ВТБ
Come on, the state bank has arrived
Давай государственный банк приехали
Sberbank VTB state bank come on,
Сбербанк ВТБ государственный банк давай
look, you've already crap the
так смотри ты уже обосрался
state bank VTB is there or not everything in
государственный банк ВТБ есть или нет в
Crimea Dava We already leaked them
Крыму всё Дава Мы те уже слили
in short Why then the government okay well VTB is a
короче А почему пому госуда ладно ну ВТБ
state bank Yes Russian Railways trains are running Well
государственный Да РЖД поезда ездят Ну
you  [ __ ] the [ __ ] How can you be so
ты обосрался [__] Как можно быть такими
weak? Yes, I don’t know, these Russian
слабыми Да я не знаю вот эти российские
bloggers, they’re all just stupid, stupid,
блогеры они все просто тупые тупо тупые
yes, he says trains go. Like, if
да говорит поезда ездят Типа так если
a train goes there, it doesn’t mean that it’s
поезд туда едет это не значит что это
your country in China. Your train goes to
твоя страна в Китай Твой поезд едет в
Belarus. Your train goes, so what?  subscribe
Белорусь твой Поезд едет и что подпишись
to my Telegram directly at once axis of wine and
на мий Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
popk tse more and more respectfully Zaga us
попк це дуже и дуже важливо Зага нас
through skarg or in new ban and even more richly
через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже багато
video I won’t show people immediately don’t show
вдео не показу людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams For this purpose, for this purpose,
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
we Mali have an operational link to write
ми Мали оперативний звязок пишиться
directly at once and while there  in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video sche tezh tsikava and korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we pon vama sing operational link
и мы пон вама пой оперативный звязок
VD togo chi show you the process YouTube
ВД того чи покаже вам проце YouTube
Glory to Ukraine
Слава Украине
write
пиши